Peter!
彼得!
Jesus Christ.
我的老天爺啊!
Can you get in please?
拜託你趕快上車好不好?
Did you put my jacket in?
你有把我的夾克放到車上嗎?
Yes.
有
And my skirt?
還有我的裙子呢?
Yes. It's in the back.
有, 它們都在後面
Now get in, it's going to be 4½ hours
現在快點上車, 我們要開4個半小時
All right.
好啦
I don't feel happy about leaving the boys.
要離開那些孩子讓我不開心
They're with your sister Alison, they will be fine.
牠們跟你的妹妹在一起 艾利森, 他們會很好的
I'd told them we'd back in time for Sunday lunch
我跟牠們說我們周日午餐前就會回來
but I don't think they believe me.
但我覺得牠們不相信我
They don't believe you Alison
牠們不相信你 艾利森
because they are dogs.
因為牠們是狗
They can't understand you.
他們不理解你在說甚麼
Yes they can.
牠們可以
No they can't.
牠們不行
Peter I am with them all day.
彼得 我整天都跟牠們在一起
They understand me perfectly.
牠們完全理解我
Well if they understand you so well,
好啊 如果他們這麼理解你
you can ask them to shit directly into the plastic bag
你可以叫他們下次散步的時候
when they take them for a walk.
直接拉屎在塑膠袋裡
or better still into the bin.
或者直接拉在垃圾桶裡會更好
Maybe they could do some pots once in a while
或許他們偶爾還可以種種盆栽
or mow the lawn.
或是除個草
Peter what is wrong with you today?
彼得 你今天有事嗎?
Is it your toenail thing?
是因為你香港腳發作嗎?
No, it's not the townail thing.
不是, 跟香港腳無關
I don't see why we have to rush down there today
我不懂為何我們今天一定要趕去
they're not getting married until tomorrow.
他們明天才結婚
I told you 3 months ago this was the plan.
我3個月前就跟你說了 計劃就是這樣
We're going up on Friday night
我們星期五晚上到
because we're meeting them in the pub.
因為我們要先在酒吧碰面
I'm going to miss my Saturday morning lengths.
我周六的晨泳時間就這樣沒了
Everyone is meeting in the pub this evening
大家晚上都會在酒吧見面
(who is everyone?),
(大家是誰?),
pre-wedding drinks.
婚禮前的小酌
We're meeting The Gang,
我們要跟那一幫人見面,
you know I used to
你知道我以前...
Tooty's Gang?
陶蒂幫?
It wasn't her gang, it was just people
不是她的幫, 只是一些大學時期
I was used to hang out with at university.
經常混在一起的人
You don't hang out with them much anymore.
你跟他們也沒有繼續聯絡
Of course I do, we had Christmas drinks
當然有啊, 我們聖誕節還有
with Davey in that pub.
跟戴維一起在酒吧喝酒啊
Who?
誰?
Davey
戴維
The fat man in the rugby shirt?
穿橄欖球衣的胖子?
Yes.
對
The one who fell over the pregnant woman.
摔倒在孕婦身上的那個?
He didn't fall.
他沒有摔到
He's ghastly.
他是身體不舒服
He was off balance.
失去平衡
He was drinking whisky.
他那時正在喝威士忌
Yes, well that's not a crime, is it?
對, 那也沒有犯罪, 對吧?
Well, we should check into the B&b first.
我們應該先去民術登記入住
What?
什麼?
We have to check into the B&b first.
我們要先去民術登記入住
Why are you saying like that?
你為什麼要那樣說?
I'm not saying like that.
我沒有那樣說啊
You are.
你有
I'm not.
我沒有
Weird.
奇怪
"B&b".
"民術"
Yes, that's what I said.
對啊, 我就是那樣說啊
Bed & Breakfast.
民 宅 住 宿
B&b.
民術
Not a "B&b, a "B&B".
不是民術, 是民宿
B&b, it's like A&e.
民術, 就像東生電視
What's that got to do with?
這跟那個有什麼關係?
Well it's like P&o.
或是像麗心郵輪
What?
什麼?
Or D&g.
或是高橘精品
What's that?
那是什麼?
Oh P I'm literally getting married tomorrow.
噢 小彼 我明天就要結婚咧
I know.
我知道
Cigarello?
抽菸?
It's been an age, but go on.
我很久沒抽了, 但 好吧
Tell. Me. Everything.
告訴我全部的事情
Well, there's not much to tell…
嗯, 其實沒甚麼好講的...
How's Alice?
艾利斯還好嗎?
Very well actually, she's good.
很好啊 她很好
It's Alison.
他叫艾利森
Toots I lost my job.
陶蒂 我失業了
Poor P.
可憐的小彼
A couple of months ago.
幾個月前的事,
Alison doesn't know.
艾利森不曉得
It's quite funny I've just been hanging
其實很好笑
around in Hyde Park in the day.
我早上都在海德公園閒晃
You'll find another
你會找到其他工作的
Yeah, well, I've got this meeting
對啊, 我下周跟艾倫。
with Alan Teasdale, next week.
提斯戴爾有個會議
I'm really hoping that comes through because,
我真的希望能有些結果,
if it doesn't I'm going to be in a bit of a pickle,
如果沒下文我會有點困窘,
you know, mortgage people
你知道的, 有房貸的人
I can't believe I am actually getting married tomorrow!
我不敢相信我明天真的要結婚了!
Yeah, I know.
是啊, 我知道
Do you remember at university
你記得我們以前
we used to do this all the time?
在大學經常這樣嗎?
Yeah, I know, we went to that pub,
對啊, 我知道, 我們去的那家酒吧,
The Plough, do you remember?
北斗七星  你記得嗎?
You used to smoke indoors then,
你以前會在室內抽菸
this feels really naughty.
感覺非常調皮
It is naughty.
是蠻調皮的
It's really naughty.
是非常調皮
Do you remember when we were really,
那你還記得我們非常,
really naughty?
非常調皮的時候嗎?
You know,
你知道嗎
I can't believe I only got to fuck you once.
我不相信我竟然只跟你上過一次床
Peter!
彼得!
Hi Alice, you look nice.
嗨 艾利斯, 你看起來很好
Are you smoking?
你在抽菸嗎?
No.
沒有
Yes.
對
Why are you standing like that?
你為什麼要站成這樣?
I need the loo. So…
我想上廁所, 所以...
Peter, when are we going to check-in at the B&b?
彼得, 我們什麼時候要去民術登記入住啊?
That's Davey.
那是戴維
Look, I need to use the credit card.
我要用信用卡
You've got your one haven't you?
你有你自己的 不是嗎?
Yeah but it's not working.
對 但刷不過
Why not?
為什麼?
Well, I don't know.
我也不知道
I can't phone them and ask.
我也不能打電話問他們
Yes you can it's 24 hour,
你可以啊 這是24小時服務的,
or India, that's awake now…
或是印度, 現在起床了...
I bought a round so I need to pay for it.
我買了一輪 所以我需要付錢
How much is it? I've got some money.
多少錢? 我這邊有些現金
It's... £486.
總共....486鎊
What!?
什麼!?
Look, I offered to buy the meal as well, because...
餐費也是我買, 因為...
Why?
為什麼?
Well, because it's the gang isn't it?
因為這我們是一幫啊, 不是嗎?
It's the university gang and I
這是大學幫 而且我
Peter!
彼得!
It's what you do.
你就是會這樣做
It's a lot of money.
這樣要很多錢耶
Just please give me the card.
拜託 把信用卡給我
It's supposed to be for emergencies only.
這本來是緊急狀況才用的
Stupid.
蠢蛋
What's the PIN number?
密碼幾號?
It's my birthday.
我的生日
Peter, it's four days after our wedding anniversary.
彼得, 那是我們結婚紀念日的後4天
Alison. I think it's time to switch the light out.
艾利森, 差不多可以關燈了
I'm reading my book.
我正在看書
You've been reading that book for about 7 months.
你那本書已經看7個月了
It's quite a complicated story
這是個很複雜的故事
You're on page 23 or something.
你還在第23頁之類的
Do you remember Toulouse?
你記得圖盧茲嗎?
Do you remember what we did?
你記得我們做了什麼嗎?
It is lights out.
把燈關了
Sorry, sorry.
對不起, 對不起
Shall I take these off Mademoiselle?
我應該把這個脫掉嗎 小姐?
That's nice.
那樣很棒
What have we here?
這是什麼東西?
Wait! Wait! Wait!
等一下! 等一下! 等一下!
I can't! I can't!
我不能! 我不能!
Is this because of Tooty?
這都是因為陶蒂嗎?
Sorry, I'm sorry
對不起, 對不起
That's OK.
沒關係
You're on my arm.
你壓到我的手臂了
Sorry.
對不起
Goodnight.
晚安
You OK?
你還好嗎?
Sorry. Sorry.
對不起, 對不起
Don't be sorry.
不用覺得對不起
What's wrong?
怎麼了?
It's nothing, it's stupid.
沒什麼, 這很愚蠢,
Stupid Peter, he's stupid
愚蠢的彼得, 他是個蠢蛋
Right.
這樣啊
He's been dirty dancing with Tooty all evening.
他整個晚上都在跟陶蒂跳貼身舞
Would he dance with me? No.
他有想要跟我跳嗎? 沒有
Well, he's a fool, isn't he?
他是個笨蛋, 不是嗎?
I asked him if he'd put my skirt in the car
我問他有沒有把我的裙子放到車上
and he said he had. But he hadn't.
他說有 但其實他沒有
I think it looks fine with the jeans.
我覺得牛仔褲也好看啊
Thank you.
謝謝你
I've got an idea.
我有一個想法,
I'm Aiden by the way.
我叫艾頓
Alison.
艾利森
That's a lovely name.
那是個很美的名字
Is it?
是嗎?
Listen Alison,
聽著艾利森,
what I like to do when I'm a little bit upset,
當我有點不開心的時候
is just go to my car and relax.
我會走到我的車上 然後放鬆
I just like to relax.
我只是想放鬆
Me too.
我也是
Really?
真的嗎?
Do want to come with me and relax?
你想要跟我一起放鬆嗎?
In my car?
在我的車上?
Yes.
好
Cool. Follow me.
很好, 跟我來
Hey Toots.
陶蒂
Hi P.
嗨 小彼
No, no, no.
不, 不, 不
I just thought you'd want a drink.
我只是想說你想要喝一杯
Oh, shit, sorry.
噢, 可惡, 對不起
Cheers!
乾杯!
Cheers.
乾杯
Listen, no, no, no Toots, listen.
聽著, 不, 不, 不 陶蒂, 聽著
I've got a really serious thing that I've gotta say,
我要講一件很認真的事情
cos I've been thinking about this
我一直在想這件事
sort of for a long time,
想了很長一段時間,
actually a lot today.
事實上今天想了很多
And I just wanted to say that I love you.
我只是想說 我愛你
Aaahh I love you to P.
噢...我也愛你 小彼
No listen to me.
不 聽我說
I love you and
我愛你
I've loved you ever since I first met you.
從我第一次見到你就開始愛你了
You know what, we could go now couldn't we?
你知道嗎, 我們現在可以私奔
Pete what are you doing?
彼得 你在幹嘛?
No c'mon we could do that!
不 快點 我們可以那樣做的!
Look I don't have much but we could go.
我沒有很多錢 但我們可以走
I really don't have much because
我真的沒有很多錢
unless Alan Teasdale
如果下周艾倫。
comes good next week I am fucked.
提斯戴爾那沒有好結果我就完了
I am totally fucked.
我徹底的完蛋
But Pete, you're really drunk, seriously.
但小彼, 你真的喝醉了, 我說真的
I'm drunk on love OK.
我沉醉在愛裡 好嗎
I'm drunk on love for you
我在你的愛裡沉醉
I love Doug, I've just married Doug.
我愛道格, 我才剛跟道格結婚
Doug!? C'mon!
道格!? 拜託!
So yesterday in the pub
所以昨天在酒吧
and you were on me and I was on you…
你在我身上 我在你身上...
Listen
聽著
you know that we could have sex right now.
你知道我們現在可以立刻上床
And I know that's what you want
而且我知道那是你想要的
because I want it too,
因為我也想要
so let's just go and do that now.
所以我們快走 然後立刻做
My cousin has a pace in Dorset, or Devon,
我表哥在多賽特郡, 或是德文郡有個房子,
but I could phone him.
我可以打給他
Peter! It's Doug. It's Doug
彼得, 道格來了, 是道格
Oooo It's Doug! I'm in the army!
喔.....道格來了! 我在軍營!
I'm Doug! I'm Brilliant!
我是道格! 我很厲害!
The things is the Moroccans,
摩洛哥人
they know how to deal with stress.
知道怎樣處理壓力
I'm the same as you,
我跟你一樣,
I get stressed out at weddings.
我在婚禮上會感到壓力
Weddings are always the same.
婚禮永遠都一樣,
People having arguments about this and that.
大家針對不同的事情在爭吵
You've just to get Moroccan about it
只要來一點摩洛哥大麻
and that suits me
而且這很適合我
because I like the Moroccan stuff.
因為我喜歡摩洛哥的東西
Jesus Christ!
我的老天爺啊!
Teach them.
調教他們
I'm gay.
我是同性戀
I’m gay.
I have been thinking about it for a while
我一直有在想這件事情
and I've realised I'm definitely gay.
然後我意識到我絕對是個同性戀
It's just that you said about relaxing in the car.
因為你說到車裡放鬆
I meant smoking a spliff.
我是說抽大麻捲菸
I didn't mean...
我不是說...
getting fresh.
親熱
Is it my breasts have they turned you gay?
是我的胸部讓你變成同性戀嗎?
No!
不是!
They're very nice.
他們非常好
Thank you.
謝謝
If I had to rate them out of 10.
如果滿分是10分
I'd say. 6.
我覺得有6分
6?
6分?
7分
Definitely, definitely 7.
一定是, 絕對是7分
That's quite good isn't it?
那還不錯, 對吧?
Yup.
對
My hairdresser is gay I think.
我想我的髮型師是個同性戀
He's called Craig.
他叫奎格
I lost my job Alison.
我失業了 艾利森
I know.
我知道
Tooty told me last night.
陶蒂昨晚跟我說了
After she told me you'd had sex together back
在他告訴我 你們以前一起混的時候
when you were in your Gang.
會上床 之後跟我講的
But you should know.
但你應該要知道
Last night a man told me my breasts were a 7
昨晚有個男人跟我說我的胸部值7分
which is actually quite high.
這是個蠻高的分數
I rang the dogs
我打給小狗了
told them we'd be back by lunchtime.
跟牠們說我們中午前會回去
Did they ask us to pick anything up?
牠們有叫我們帶什麼東西回去嗎?
Don't be stupid Peter. They're dogs.
別傻了 彼得 牠們是狗
If you just
如果你...
Not a word.
別再說了